in this video we'll be using free
在这段视频中 我们将使用免费
software caden live to do this speed
软件卡登活着就是为了做到这一点
effect with a blur we'll be increasing
效果模糊 我们将增加
the speed quite a bit and we'll also be
速度相当快 我们也会
doing slow and we'll be doing this using
做得很慢 我们将使用
the speed remapping tool in caden life
CADEN LIFE中的速度映射工具
so to get started we'll drag our video
因此 在开始之前 我们将拖动我们的视频
clip down this is just drone video
剪辑下来这只是一段无人机视频
footage um from a gopro
GoPro拍摄的素材
so it's a mp4 format and we're going to
所以这是一种MP4格式 我们将
go to the point that we want right now
去到我们现在想要的点上
everything's just slow
一切都很慢
and so this is the part we want to be
这就是我们想要成为的一部分
speeding up this sort of pan around
加快这种平底锅的速度
these bikers on top of this ramp
在这个坡道上的这些摩托车手
we'll start by trimming the clip just a
我们将从剪辑开始只修剪一段
little bit so that it starts in where we
所以它从我们开始的地方开始
want and we'll trim it out so it'll end
想要 我们会把它修剪掉 这样它就会结束
here just we're just trimming the start
在这里我们只是在调整开始
and end of the clip not adjusting speed
和结束的剪辑不调整速度
at all yet so this will be the clip that
所以这将是一段
we're working with
我们正在与
we can right click and go to time remap
我们可以右键单击并转到时间重新映射
and that brings up this interface down
这会使此接口关闭
here in the bottom left hand corner and
在这里的左下角
we can see we have our source clip on
我们可以看到我们已经打开了我们的源剪辑
the top and then our output on the
顶部 然后是我们在
bottom and this lets us remap or change
底部 这允许我们重新映射或更改
the time of the video so what we're
视频的时间 所以我们是
going to do is we're going to click here
我们要做的就是点击这里
to add a keyframe
添加关键帧的步骤
and we'll go forward to the point we
我们将继续我们的观点
want the time to change back
想要时间换回来吗？
to so it all in between there's going to
所以这一切之间都会有
be fast speed we'll click to add another
快点 我们将点击添加另一个
keyframe and then if we drag this lower
关键帧 然后如果我们将其拖低
one we're basically telling it fit
我们基本上可以说它很适合
everything that was going to be in there
所有要放在里面的东西
into this a tiny time frame so it makes
在一个很小的时间范围内 所以它
it basically
它基本上是
almost nine times faster so so over this
几乎快了九倍 所以在这上面
time it's going to very quickly play all
现在它很快就会播放所有
what was normally going to be about
通常情况下会发生什么
three or four seconds and play it in
三四秒钟 然后把它放进去
about half a second
大约半秒
and then we can do the same thing later
然后我们可以稍后再做同样的事情
on in the video we can add another
在视频中 我们可以添加另一个
keyframe and we can either manually move
关键帧 我们可以手动移动
drag the node like we did
像我们一样拖动节点
or we can just come down below so we'll
或者我们可以直接到下面来 这样我们就
add these two key frames and then in
添加这两个关键帧 然后在
between these two we'll just change the
在这两个之间 我们只需更改
speed and we can change it manually by
速度 我们可以通过手动更改它
just typing in 50 and that'll make it 50
只需输入50 就会变成50
percent or half the speed that it
%或一半的速度
normally was
通常情况下
and this is shot at um i think the shot
这是在 嗯 我想这一枪
at 120 fps so we can slow it down it'll
120帧/秒 这样我们就可以放慢速度
still look nice and smooth
仍然看起来很好很流畅
over here under effects
在这里的影响下
we can click on this
我们可以点击这个
keyframe and we'll add a blur we'll add
关键帧 我们将添加一个模糊 我们将添加
a box blur and we'll add a keyframe in
一个长方体模糊 我们将在
and we have to actually add it up here
我们必须在这里把它加起来
at
在…
on the effect we have to add the
在效果上 我们必须添加
keyframes in the same point
同一点上的关键帧
this is going to create a blur and
这将会产生一个模糊的
that's because if we just speed up it
这是因为如果我们只是加快速度
looks a little bit unnatural and so this
看起来有点不自然 所以这个
way we can blur while we're moving
当我们移动时 我们可以模糊的方式
quickly it kind of simulates what that
很快 它就有点模拟了
motion blur will look like
运动模糊将看起来像
and we'll add this blur on the
我们将把这个模糊添加到
horizontal axis instead of the vertical
水平轴而不是垂直轴
and then that way since we're moving
然后这样 因为我们要搬家了
horizontally that's just kind of the
从水平上看 这只是一种
direction we want the blur
我们想要模糊的方向
and we can change the way that it enters
我们可以改变它进入的方式
into this blur change it to smooth
变成这个模糊 把它变得平滑
and so here's the final result
这就是最终的结果
so a really good tool to get familiar
所以这是一个非常好的熟悉工具
with this time remapping hopefully you
有了这个时间重新映射 希望你
found this video informative go ahead
我觉得这段视频很有见地 继续
and leave your questions comments below
并在下面留下您的问题和评论
if you have any and look forward to
如果你有 并期待着
catching you in the next video
在下一个视频中看到你
you
你